<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mahesh Jandwani</title>
    <link>https://maheshjandwani.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mahesh Jandwani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2023, Mahesh Jandwani</copyright><atom:link href="https://maheshjandwani.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://maheshjandwani.tech/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maheshjandwani.tech/about/</guid>
      <description>About Hello 👋 I’m Mahesh Jandwani. I live in Abu Road, Rajasthan.
I’m a security engineer at ACKO working on the cloud and product security. I’ve done my studies in Computer Science and Engineering from the JECRC University of Jaipur, Rajasthan.
Previously, I’ve worked as a Penetration Tester intern at ThreatHawk and Cloud Security Associate at Virtually Testing Foundation.
Contact You can reach me by email at maheshjhandwani9999@gmail.com. You can also connect with me on LinkedIn, GitHub, and Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://maheshjandwani.tech/certificates/my-certificates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maheshjandwani.tech/certificates/my-certificates/</guid>
      <description>Certificates Google Cloud Certified Professional Cloud Security Engineer EC-Council - Certified Ethical Hacker v11 AWS Cloud Quest: Cloud Practitioner Google Workspace Security Microsoft Certified: Security Engineer Associate Microsoft Certified: Identity &amp;amp; Access Management Microsoft Certified: Azure Security Engineer Associate Microsoft 365 Certified: Security Administrator Microsoft Certified: Security Operations Analyst Associate Microsoft Certified: Security, Compliance, Identity Fundamentals CCNP: Core Networking CCNA v7: Introduction to Networks Cisco CyberOps Associate Cisco Cybersecurity Essentials Splunk Infrastructure Overview Splunk User Behaviour Analytics Splunk Fundamentals </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
